eattravellife.com 2019-04-07

# privacy policy - Eat Travel Life

**Privacy Policy-**

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this website (https://www.eattravellife.com)

**WHAT WE COLLECT AND HOW IT IS USED:**

**We will collect any information you voluntarily submit to our site:**  We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form. In addition, you are able to create a user profile, which allows you to create a username and password. We will store the username, but your password will not be visible in our records.  
**We may collect information you share from other accounts:**  We may receive information about you from other sources. You may link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile. If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.  
**We collect some statistical information automatically:**  We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked. This information is used only for statistical purposes.  
**We do collect cookies:**  We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

**WHAT ARE WE DOING WITH YOUR INFORMATION WHEN WE COLLECT IT?**

We don’t keep this information for nefarious purposes or to browse on our own for fun. Instead, this data is collected mostly for statistical purposes as listed below.

  * To create your user account for use on the Website  
To send promotional information to you via our newsletter or weekly email. Each email promotion via Feedburner provides an easy method to opt-out of future mailings.  
To operate and maintain the Website properly  
To easily respond to you when you leave a comment on our post or send a message via our email contact form  
To provide you, as a Website user, with proper support and/or to send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;  
To track and measure advertising on the Website;  
To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

**WHAT DO THIRD PARTIES DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT ON THE WEBSITE?**

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.  
Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

**The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:**

Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

Feedburner – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. Other activities performed by Feedburner may include the collection (e.g., via sign-up forms) and storage of personal data in order to create and use distribution lists, send marketing email campaigns, and place online advertisements), and the transfer of personal data to certain of Feedburner’s sub-processors (who perform some critical services, such as helping Feedburner prevent abuse and providing support to our customers). Please refer to Feedburner’s privacy policy for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

**WHAT WE DO WITH ANONYMOUS DATA:**

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

**PUBLIC USER INFORMATION:**

If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website.

You may also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and Google Account.

Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

**WHAT HAPPENS TO THE COOKIES STORED?**

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the Website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

**OUR ADVERTISING PROGRAMS AND WHAT THEY USE OF YOUR INFORMATION:**

** ** **Display Ads-**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.  
**Retargeting Ads-**  
From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, Twitter or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.  
**Affiliate Program Participation-**  
The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR OUR NEWSLETTER:**

On the Website, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

**YOUR RIGHTS IN REGARDS TO THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU SHARE WITH US AS A USER OR FOLLOWER:**

Opt-out – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at itsjustregina@gmail.com to be removed from our mailing list.

Access – You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to itsjustregina@gmail.com.

Amend – You may contact us at itsjustregina@gmail.com to amend or update your personal information.

Forget – In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to itsjustregina@gmail.com.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

**SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**CHILDREN’S INFORMATION:**

The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at itsjustregina@gmail.com and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**CONTACT INFORMATION:**

At any time, please contact us at itsjustregina@gmail.com for questions related to this Privacy Policy.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on May 22, 2018. If you have any questions feel free to contact me directly: itsjustregina@gmail.com
